bizagi.com 2018-06-26

# Privacy Policy

Bizagi Group Limited and its Affiliates ( “Bizagi”) is committed to respecting the privacy of visitors to its websites (“Visitors”), individuals who register to use the Services as defined below (“Customers”), and individuals who register to attend Bizagi’s corporate events (“Attendees”). As a result, Bizagi has developed this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement describes Bizagi’s privacy practices in relation to the use of the Bizagi websites and the related applications, services, training classes, eBooks, and programs offered by Bizagi (collectively, the “Services”), as well as individuals’ choices regarding use, access and correction of choices regarding use, access and correction of personal information. Other Information Bizagi collects may include your IP Address and additional information gathered through our weblogs and cookies (see below).

This Privacy Statement lets you know how Bizagi collects and uses your personal information, how you can control its use, and describes our practices regarding information collected from the different Bizagi sites that link or refer to this Privacy Statement (such as our websites, computer or mobile software applications, social media pages and HTML-formatted e-mail messages), as well as through offline sales and marketing activities (collectively, the "Channels").

The Channels may provide links to or the ability to connect with non-Bizagi websites, services, social networks or applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow the third party to collect or share information about you. Those third-party websites or services are beyond our control. We encourage you to check the privacy policies and terms of use of any non-Bizagi website or service before providing your Personal Information to them.

If you have questions or complaints regarding Bizagi’s Privacy Statement or associated practices, please contact us by emailing at [privacy@bizagi.com](mailto:privacy@bizagi.com). 

## 1\. Scope

This Privacy Statement covers the information practices, including how Bizagi collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, of websites that link to this Privacy Statement (collectively referred to as “Bizagi’s Websites”). 

**1.1.** https://www.bizagi.com/en/community/connectors-xchange is an online product exchange for on-demand Bizagi connectors and third parties. When Bizagi posts connectors and the connector links to this Privacy Statement, this Privacy Statement applies. When connectors are posted by third parties, the privacy statement of the third party applies, and this Privacy Statement does not apply.

**1.2.** https://www.bizagi.com/en/community/widget-xchange is an online widget exchange for on-demand Bizagi widgets and third parties. When Bizagi posts widgets and those widgets link to this Privacy Statement, this Privacy Statement applies. When widgets are posted by third parties, the privacy statement of the third party applies, and this Privacy Statement does not apply.  
Bizagi’s Websites may contain links to other Channels. The information practices or the content of such other websites is governed by the privacy statements of those other websites. Bizagi encourages you to review the privacy statements of other websites to understand their information practices. 

## 2\. Collection of Personal Information

When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services, in registering to use Bizagi’s Websites or other Services, or in registering for an event, Bizagi requires you to provide your personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address (“Contact Information”). When purchasing the Services or registering for an event, Bizagi may also require you to provide your billing information, such as billing name and address, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Services (“Billing Information”). Bizagi may also ask you to provide additional information, such as annual company revenues, number of employees, or industry (“Optional Information”). When applying for a job as a Visitor, Bizagi may also require you to submit additional personal information as well as a resume or curriculum vitae (“Applicant Information”). Contact Information, Billing Information, Applicant Information, Optional Information and any other information you submit to Bizagi to or through the Services are referred to collectively as “Data.”

As you navigate Bizagi’s Web sites, Bizagi may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies (“Website Tools”). Website Tools information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your device used to connect to the website, and the actions you take on Bizagi’s Websites (such as the Webpages viewed and the links clicked). 

From time to time, Bizagi and our third-party service providers may collect both Personal Information and Other Information from a variety of sources that fall into three categories: 1. Direct Interactions: From your use of and interaction with us through the Channels and other activities such as account creation, submission of registrations and forms, or sales inquiries and transactions; 2. Publicly Available Data / Data from Third Parties: Data from Automated Interactions on non-Bizagi Websites, or other data you may have made publicly available, such as social media posts, or data provided by third-party sources, such as marketing opt-in lists, or data aggregators; and, 3. Automated Interactions: From the use of technologies such as electronic communication protocols, cookies, embedded URLs or pixels, or widgets, buttons and tools.

The information that Bizagi collects, either directly or indirectly, may be combined to help us improve its overall accuracy and completeness and to help us better tailor our interactions with you.

Bizagi may collect information about the training classes you take. Bizagi may collect your name, your role and classes you complete. Bizagi may also collect test scores from these classes. We may collect this information from you or your employer. 

## 3\. Use of information collected

Bizagi will use your Data to respond to requests you may make of us. Bizagi may also use your Data to contact you and provide general information about our products, Services, partners, promotions, and events. Bizagi may use the information collected to improve the Bizagi Websites and Services better. Bizagi may use your Data and other information to notify you about new product releases and service developments and to advertise Bizagi's products and Services by this Privacy Statement. Your visit to Bizagi’s Websites, marketing experience, and communications may be tailored to your interests based on your Data. Bizagi may pass your contact information to the appropriate Bizagi distributor or reseller for further follow-up related to your interests. Also, Bizagi may share your Data with specific partners that offer complementary products and services and may share Other Information with third parties to facilitate interest-based advertising. If you download products from our Channels, Bizagi uses your Data to confirm specific information about your order (for example, that you did not experience problems in the download process); discuss the downloaded products; or provide marketing or sales information ab out related products and Services. Bizagi also may use Personal Information to contact you, confirm compliance with licensing and other terms of use, and may share it with your company.

Bizagi also uses Data about Bizagi Attendees to plan and host corporate events, host online forums and social networks in which event Attendees may participate, and to populate online profiles for Attendees on Bizagi’s Websites. 

Bizagi may also use Data about Bizagi Customers and Attendees for marketing purposes. 

Bizagi may also receive information about Customers and Attendees from other sources, including third parties from whom Bizagi has purchased data, and combine this information with Data Bizagi already has about you. This information helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and create more tailored advertising to provide products and services that may be of interest to you. Bizagi may use your Data to help create and personalize content on our Channels, facilitate your use of the Channels (for example, to facilitate navigation and the login process, avoid duplicate data entry, enhance security, keep track of shopping cart additions and preserve order information between sessions), improve quality, track marketing campaign responsiveness (including online advertising and e-mail marketing), and evaluate page response rates. Bizagi uses Website Tools to operate and improve the Bizagi Websites. Bizagi may also use Website Tools alone or in combination with Data about Bizagi Customers and Data about Bizagi Attendees to provide personalized information about Bizagi. 

Bizagi partners with third parties to display advertising on Bizagi’s Websites and Services or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use cookies, or similar technologies provide you advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), or if you are located in the European Union click here. Please note you will continue receiving generic ads. Bizagi may use your Data to interact with you on third-party social networks. Bizagi's interactions with you on a third party social network would be subject to that network's privacy policies and terms of use.

Bizagi does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. Bizagi may share information with other companies that work on Bizagi’s behalf or that partner with Bizagi. Bizagi will share personal information to meet any applicable law, regulation or lawful request by public authorities, including for national security or law enforcement requirements.

Bizagi’s policy is to restrict affiliates, subsidiaries, agents, contractors or partners from using shared information in any way other than to provide Services for Bizagi or Services for the collaboration in which they and Bizagi are engaged. 

**3.1. Bizagi’s legitimate interest** Each of the use cases below constitutes a legitimate interest of Bizagi to process or use Personal Data. If you do not agree, you may object to Bizagi’s processing or use of your Personal Data as set out below.

_Questionnaires and surveys._ Bizagi may invite you to participate in questionnaires and surveys. These questionnaires and surveys will generally be designed in a way that they can be answered without any Personal Data. If you nonetheless enter Personal Data in a questionnaire or survey, Bizagi may use such Personal Data to improve its products and services. 

_Creation of anonymized data sets._ Bizagi may anonymize Personal Data provided under this Privacy Statement to create anonymized data sets, which will then be used to improve its and its affiliates’ products and services. 

_In order to keep you up-to-date/request feedback._ Within an existing business relationship between Customer and Bizagi, Bizagi may inform Customer, where permitted by local laws, about its products or services (including webinars, seminars or events) which are similar or relate to such products and services you have already purchased or used from Bizagi. Furthermore, where you have attended a webinar, seminar or event of Bizagi or purchased Services from Bizagi, Bizagi may contact you for feedback regarding the improvement of the relevant webinar, seminar, event, product or service. 

## 4\. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Technologies

Bizagi uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the Bizagi Websites (“Website Tools”). As described more fully below, our partners and Bizagi use these cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer Websites and Services, track users’ movements around our Websites and Services, serve targeted advertisements and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This section describes the types of Website Tools Information used on the Bizagi Web sites and Services, and how this information may be used.

**4.1. Cookies:** A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive (“Cookies”). It enables Bizagi’s Websites to identify your computer and collect information about how you browse Bizagi’s Websites. Cookies allow Bizagi’s Websites to: 1. store your preferences to present content, options or functions that are specific to you; and, 2. enable us to see information like how many people use the website and what pages they tend to visit.

**4.1.1.** Bizagi may use cookies to analyze our web traffic using an analytics package; aggregated usage data helps us improve the website structure, design, content, and functions; identify whether you are signed in to Bizagi’s Websites; a cookie allows us to check whether you are signed in to the site; test content on our website.   
Please be aware that Cookies do not provide us with access to your computer or any information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us. 

**4.1.2. Managing Cookie Preferences:** You can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how the Bizagi Websites use cookies. If you do not want Bizagi’s Websites to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, please note that doing this may affect how Bizagi’s Websites function. Some pages and services may become unavailable to you. Unless you have changed your browser to refuse cookies, Bizagi’s Websites will issue cookies when you visit them. 

**4.1.2.1** Managing information about you when you fill in a form or provide your details on Bizagi’s Websites, you will see one or more tickboxes allowing you to: 

  * Opt-in to receive marketing communications from us by email, telephone, text message or post. 
  * Opt-in to receive marketing communications from our third-party partners by email, telephone, text message or post. 
  * If you have agreed that Bizagi can use your information for marketing purposes, you can change your mind quickly by managing your preferences [here](http://go.bizagi.com/Manage_your_email_preference.html).

**4.1.3. Flash Cookies:** Bizagi may use Flash cookies, also known as "local shared objects," on our electronic Channels that employ Flash technology. Flash cookies are used to remember the site's settings to personalize the look and feel of the site. Like regular cookies, Flash cookies are represented as small files on your computer. One method of preventing Flash cookies from being placed is to adjust your preferences in the Macromedia website privacy settings panel at macromedia.com. 

**4.2. Embedded URLs:** Bizagi may use a tracking technique that employs embedded URLs to allow the use of the electronic Channels without cookies. Embedded URLs allow limited information to follow you as you navigate the electronic Channels, but are not associated with Data and are not used beyond the session. 

**4.3. Embedded Pixels and Similar Technologies:** On the electronic Channels, Bizagi and its service providers may use embedded pixel technologies to identify unique user visits (as opposed to aggregate hits) and for advertising purposes. Also, embedded pixels or other technologies may be used in e-mails and our online display advertising to provide information on when the e-mail or ad was opened to track marketing campaign responsiveness; information collected using these technologies may be associated with the recipient's e-mail address. 

**4.4. Widgets, Buttons, and Tools:** Our electronic Channels may include widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g., links to bookmarked sites), along with buttons or other tools that link to other companies' services (e.g., a "Like" button or third-party map). The widget, button or tool may collect and automatically send Data, such as your e-mail address, or other information (such as your browser information, or IP address), to a third party. Cookies may also be set or used by the widgets, buttons or tools to enable them to function properly or for other purposes, which may include advertising. Information collected or used by a widget, button or tool, including cookie settings and preferences, is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. 

**4.5. Physical Location:** Bizagi may collect and share the physical location of your device for purposes consistent with this Privacy Statement, such as to provide you with personalized location-based services or content. In some instances, you may be permitted to allow or deny such use of your device's location, but if you choose to deny such use, we may not be able to provide you with the applicable personalized services or content. 

**4.6. Log Files, IP Addresses, URLs and Other Data:** As is true of most websites, Bizagi gathers specific information automatically to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer Bizagi’s Websites and Services. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), device and application identification numbers, your location, your browser type, your Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, the pages and files you viewed, your searches, your operating system and system configuration information, and date/time stamps associated with your usage. Due to Internet communications standards, when you visit or use Bizagi’s Websites and Services, Bizagi automatically receives the URL of the website from which you came and the website to which you go when you leave Bizagi’s Websites. This information is used to analyze overall trends, to help us improve Bizagi’s Websites and Services, to track and aggregate non-personal information, and to provide Bizagi’s Websites and Services. For example, Bizagi uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Bizagi’s Websites. Bizagi also collects IP addresses from Customers when they log into the Services as part of the Bizagi’s “Identity Confirmation” and “IP Range Restrictions” security features. 

**4.7. Social Media Features and Single Sign-on:** Bizagi’s Websites may use social media features, such as the LinkedIn “like” button (“Social Media Features”). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Bizagi Websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on Bizagi’s Websites to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third-party social media network to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on Bizagi’s Websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features. Bizagi also allows you to log in to certain of Bizagi’s Websites and Services using sign-in services such as Linkedin, Microsoft and Google. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign-up form. 

**4.8. Do Not Track:** Currently, various browsers — including Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari — offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to websites’ visited by the user about the user's browser DNT preference setting. Bizagi does not currently commit to responding to browsers' DNT signals concerning the Bizagi Websites, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent. Bizagi takes privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard. 

## 5\. Public forums refer a contact, and customer testimonials

Bizagi may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on the Bizagi Websites. Any personal information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. Bizagi is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.

Customers and Visitors may elect to use Bizagi’s referral program to inform contacts about Bizagi’s Websites and Services. When using the referral program, Bizagi requests the contact’s name and email address. Bizagi will automatically send the contact a one–time email inviting him or her to visit Bizagi’s Websites. Bizagi does not store this information.

Bizagi posts a list of Customers and testimonials on Bizagi’s Websites that contain information such as Customer names and titles. Bizagi obtains the consent of each Customer before posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials. 

## 6\. Sharing of information collected

**6.1. Service Providers:** Bizagi may share Data about Bizagi Visitors, Customers and Attendees with Bizagi’s contracted service providers so that these service providers can provide services on our behalf. These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide the requested services to us. Without limiting the preceding, Bizagi may also share Data about Bizagi Visitors, Customers and Attendees with Bizagi’s service providers to ensure the quality of information provided, and with third-party social networking and media websites, such as LinkedIn, for marketing and advertising on those websites. Unless described in this Privacy Statement, Bizagi does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

**6.2. Bizagi Affiliates:** Bizagi may share Data about Bizagi Customers with other companies to work with them, including affiliates of the Bizagi corporate group. 

**6.3. Business Partners:** From time to time, Bizagi may partner with other companies to jointly offer products, services, or programs. If you purchase, explicitly express interest in, or register for a jointly–offered product, service, or program from or through Bizagi, Bizagi may share Data about Customers collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our partner(s). Bizagi does not control our business partners’ use of the Data about Bizagi’s Customers collected by us, and their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to purchase or explicitly express interest in a jointly-offered product or services.

Bizagi does not share Data about Bizagi Attendees with business partners unless: (1) you expressly opt-in to such sharing via an event registration form; or (2) you attend a Bizagi event and allow or any of its business partners to scan your attendee badge. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to opt-in via event registration forms and elect not to have your badge scanned at Bizagi events. If you decide to share your information with business partners in the manners described above, your information will be subject to the business partners’ respective privacy statements. 

**6.4. Third Parties:** Section 4 of this Privacy Statement, Website Tools, specifically addresses the information third parties or Bizagi collects through cookies and web beacons, and how you can control cookies through your Web browsers. Bizagi may also disclose your personal information to any third party with your prior consent. 

**6.5. Compelled Disclosure:** Bizagi reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if Bizagi reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect Bizagi’s rights and to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. 

## 7\. International transfer of information collected

Bizagi is a global corporation and has developed global data security practices designed to ensure that your personal information is appropriately protected. Please note that personal information may be transferred, accessed and stored globally as necessary for the uses and disclosures stated above by this policy. By providing your personal information, you consent to Bizagi transferring your personal information to its affiliates globally and to third-party entities that provide services to Bizagi.

Bizagi has implemented appropriate safeguards for transfers of personal information originating from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to Bizagi affiliates and unaffiliated third parties located outside the EEA, including: 

  * Where required, Bizagi implements Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the EU Commission or similar contractual clauses in other jurisdictions. This includes transfers to Bizagi affiliates and unaffiliated third parties located outside the EEA. 

## 8\. Communications preferences

Bizagi offers Visitors, Customers, and Attendees who provide contact information a means to choose how Bizagi uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of Bizagi’s marketing emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe here or by contacting us using the information in the “Contacting Us" section below.

## 9\. Data subject rights

You may request to review, correct, delete or otherwise modify any of the personal information that you have previously provided to us through Bizagi’s Websites and Services. If you have registered for an account with Bizagi, you may update your user settings, profile, organization’s settings or event registration by logging into the applicable Bizagi’s Websites or Services with your username and password and editing your settings or profile. To update your billing information, discontinue your account, and request return or deletion of the Data associated with your account, please contact us by emailing at [privacy@bizagi.com](mailto:privacy@bizagi.com).

In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information that you have provided to us suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would want to put on our use of your Personal Information that you have provided to us.

While the majority of questions and issues related to access can be handled quickly, complex requests may take more research and time. In such cases, issues will be addressed, or you will be contacted regarding the nature of the problem and appropriate next steps, within thirty days. 

**9.1. Retention and Deletion** Bizagi will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active; as needed to provide you Services; as needed for the purposes outlined in this Policy or at the time of collection; as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements; or to the extent permitted by law.

At the end of the retention period, Bizagi will delete your Personal Information in a manner designed to ensure that it cannot be reconstructed or read. 

## 10\. Security

The security of your Data is significant to Bizagi. Bizagi uses physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect your Data from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

If your Personal Information is acquired or is reasonably believed to have been obtained, by an unauthorized person and applicable law requires notification, Bizagi will notify you by e-mail or mail. Bizagi will give you notice promptly, consistent with the reasonable needs of law enforcement and Bizagi to determine the scope of the breach and to investigate and restore the integrity of the data system. 

## 11\. Sensitive Information

Bizagi asks you to avoid sending and sharing any sensitive Personal Information with us(e.g., government-issued or financial account numbers, information related to the racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, genetic, or biometric data, criminal background or trade union membership). 

## 12\. Children's Privacy

As a company focused on serving the needs of businesses, Bizagi's Channels are not directed to minors, and Bizagi does not promote or market its services to children, except as part of specific educational outreach programs with parental permission. If you believe that Bizagi has mistakenly or unintentionally collected personal information of a minor through our Channels without appropriate consent, please notify us through our inquiry form so that Bizagi may immediately delete the Data from our servers and make any other necessary corrections. Additionally, please use this same form to request removal of content or information that was posted to our Channels when the registered user was under the age of 18. Please note that such requests may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, as, for example, some of your content may have been reposted by another user. 

## 13\. Changes to this Privacy Statement

Bizagi may reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement. Bizagi will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through Bizagi’s Websites at least thirty (30) business days before the change taking effect. 

## 14\. Contacting us

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of Bizagi’s Websites and Services should be directed to Bizagi Privacy by e-mailing us at [privacy@bizagi.com](mailto:privacy@bizagi.com).
